New York State Department of Labor Benefits Files 6291
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State Department of Labor Benefits Files
1936-1971
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State Department of Labor
6291
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Records.
6717809
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 11, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 31, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Employee fringe benefits -- New York (State); New York (State).; New York (State). Dept. of Labor.
6717809
- Bens. - Elig. General Formulas - no. 1 (1938-1955) (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Ben. - Elig. Remuneration, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- R&S - Ben. - Elig. Supplemental Unemployment Benefits, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- R&S - Ben. - Elig. Time Worked, 1954-1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Ben. Elig. Wages Paid, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- R&S - Ben. Elig. General - Formulas - no. 2 (1957 - (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Ben. - Formula Proposed Changes, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Ben. - Formula - Annual Earning General, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Ben. Formula - Annual Earnings General, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Ben. - Formula - Pkg. Bill Employer Technical Com., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Ben. - Formula - Pkg. Bill General - no. 1 (1947-1948) (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Ben. - Formula - Pkg. Bill Labor Technical Comm., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Ben. - Formula - Pkg. Bill Sets of Materials, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Ben. Gen. Exper. General No. 2 (1953-1961) (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Ben. Gen. Exper. General - no. 1 (1939-1950) (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Bens. - Improper Payts. General, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Bens. - Interst. - Appeals General (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Bens. - Interst. - Benefit Arrangement General - No, 3 (1/1/49), 1949 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Bens. - Interst. - Benefit Arrangement General - no. 2 (10/47-12/48), 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Bens. - Interst. Benefit Arrangement General - no. 1 (11/46-9/47), 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Bens. - Interst. - Benefit Plan General, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Bens. Interst. - Combined Wage General, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Bens. - Interst. - General General, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Bens. - Interst, - Statistics General, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- R&S - Ben. - Ledger 1945-46, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- R&S - Ben. - Ledger 1944-45, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- R&S - Ben. - Ledger 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- R&S - Ben. - Ledger 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Ben. Partial, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Bens. Pension Deductions, 1960-1964 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- R&S - Bens. - Post-War General, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- R&S - Bens. - Proc. Bi-Weekly RPTG., 1953 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- R&S - Ben. - Proc. Decentralization, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- R&S - Ben. - Proc. Delay in Filing, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- R&S - Bens. - Proc. Experimental Offices, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Bens. - Proc. General - no. 3 (1947-1959) (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Bens. - Proc. General - no. 2 (1939-1946) (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Bens. - Proc. General - no. 1 (1936-1938) (Box 1, Folder 38)
- R&S - Bens. - Proc. Mail Certification, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- R&S - Ben. - Proc. Mass Layoff, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- R&S - Ben. - Proc. Over-the-Counter Payments, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- R&S - Ben. - Proc. Plans A, B, C, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- R&S - Bens. - Proc. Request Reporting, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- R&S - Bens. - Proc. Time-Lapse, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Ben. Puerto Rico - no. 4 (1966 - ) (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Joint Conference of the Advisory Council on Employment and Unemployment Insurance and the Division of Employment Schedule and Division of Employment Organization Chart, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Federal Emergency Employment Act and Manpower Revenue Sharing Act, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Food Stamp Act Amendment, H.R. 1 Analysis (DoL), and State Welfare Reform Operations and Activities, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- 1971 Joint Conference of the Advisory Council on Employment and Unemployment Insurance and the Division of Employment (Misc.) (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Joint Conference of the Advisory Council on Employment and Unemployment Insurance and the Division of Employment (Misc.), 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Partial Unemployment Study (Part 1), 1964 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Partial Unemployment Study (Part 2), 1964 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Prevailing Wage Surveys (Part 1) 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Prevailing Wage Studies (Part 2) 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Prevailing Wage Studies (Part 3) 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- NYS and Interstate Claims from Puerto Rico (Part 1), 1960-1964 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- NYS and Interstate Claims from Puerto Rico (Part 2), 1960-1964 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Repeat Benefits: General, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Bureau of Research and Statistics: Retroactive Benefits Payments, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Benefits Statistics: Active Files, 1943-1958 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Benefits Statistics: Amount of Benefits, 1941-1961 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Benefits Statistics: Annual Central Summary and Day-Base Plan, 1938-1946 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Benefits Statistics: Estimated U.I. Claims - Annual and Monthly (62-64), 1947-1964 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Benefits Statistics: General No.1-2 (1942-1962) (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Veteran's Benefits: Appeals and DPUI, Benefits Supplements, 1944-1953 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Benefits Statistics: Utica - 1940 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Veteran's Benefits: General, 1942-1958 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Veteran's Benefits: Statistics, 1940-1947 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Conference on Employment Security Objectives: Financing Benefits, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Report on the Subject of Experience Rating by NY Unemployment Insurance State Advisory Council, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Repot on the Subject of Experience Rating by NY Unemployment Insurance State Advisory Council, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 25)